https://nydancestore.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
Best & NewAll productsBest SellersNewCouture leotardsAll productsCamisoleTankShort sleeveCap Sleeve3/4 SleeveLong sleeveHalterLadies & Girls DancewearAll productsBallet ClassLeotardsUnitardsBiketardsWarm-upsLeg warmersSweaters-TopsSkirtsShortsPantsLeggingsUnitards-BiketardsUrban Jazz YogaTopsPantsShortsSweatersBallroom and LatinDressesSkirtsTopsFlamencoTights-Socks-LeggingsDressesSkirtsJacketsFashionUnderwearKids - ClassAll productsLeotardsCamisoleShort sleeveLong sleeveTankCap SleeveWarm-upsShortsUnitards-BiketardsSweatersLeg warmersTops & T-shirtsTights & LegginsShorts & PantsTutusDresses and SkirtsSweater & Cross-overAccessoriesDance ShoesAcademia pointe shoesPrêt-à-ballet pointe shoesSoft shoesDemi-pointeSneakersBallroom shoesTap shoesJazz shoesCharacter shoesStage TutusPointe shoesAll productsF.R. Duval La Pointe NumeroAcademia pointe shoesPrêt-à-ballet pointe shoes600 SeriesStage lineEssentialsSquare boxGerman TraditionK.H. Martin POINTISSIMAPointe Shoe AccessoriesBallet SlippersAll productsSplit soleClassic CanvasStretch CanvasLeatherVeganMeshFull soleLeatherVeganMeshAll Dance shoesAll productsBallroom and LatinSneakersTap shoesJazz shoesFlamencoCharacter shoesTeacher's ShoesBootiesBallet bootsCharacter bootsStage BootsFoot thongs-ModernGhilliesEastern danceYouthTango shoesSoft toe-Demi-pointeMen & BoysAll productsLeotardsBalletUnitards-BiketardsTops & T-ShirtsShortsPantsSweatersMen's tightsUnderwearAccessories & BagsAll productsFootwear AccessoriesBagsKeyringsPosters-MagnetsJewelryHair AccessoriesCDs-DVDsPhone AccessoriesMiscStationeryPostcards-Greeting cardsProductos dermatógicosMasksLimited EditionAll productsPointe ShoesBallet SlippersStage TutusDance ShoesDancewearKidsMen DancewearAccessoriesFINAL CHANCEAll productsPointe shoesBallet slippersStage TutusDance ShoesAll DancewearKidsMen dancewearAccessories
Account
Home
Cookie Popup Privacy
PRIVACY and COOKIES POLICY
Privacy policy / Protection of personal data
Privacy
SANSHA
is committed to protecting your online privacy. When you use SANSHA website, SANSHA will collect any personal information voluntarily provided by the customer. This information may be:
Name, address, phone number, delivery address, email address, birth date, credit card details, school’s name, teacher’s name
and details of the items you've ordered.
This is done to ensure:
1. the smooth processing & delivery of your order, or to contact you if there is a problem with your order.
2. ease of use of any subsequent visits you may make to our website as easy as possible, meaning you don't have to resubmit certain information each time you shop with us.
3. information related to the goods bought with us previously.
4. ugrade our customer database to help us improve our service and product range and to help us attract similar customers. Third party
companies software and extentions may be used.
By accessing our Site, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy and to have your personal data provided to us, processed as per this Privacy Policy.
Security
SANSHA web site uses encryption technology (SSL) to ensure that your transactions are confidential and protected. When you proceed to make your purchase, your browser connects to the secure section of SANSHA website. Your browser will show a small padlock indicating that the connection is secure. SANSHA also uses Visa® or Mastercard® safety services to ensure our payment cards are as secure as possible. These services help protect your card against fraudulent use online. If you forget your Visa® or Mastercard®
passwords, please contact the service providers directly. SANSHA does not have nor keep this information.
E-Mail Correspondence
SANSHA provides on its website e-mail addresses for questions or comments, as well as on-line bulletin boards for support.
In the process of receiving and responding to such requests, we may collect personal information about you, such as your email address or any other personal data contained in the body of your email. By allowing you to send us these requests, we are not attempting to solicit personal information from you. We only use the information for the purpose of responding to your questions and/or comments or to provide customer support. In cases related to exchanges-refunds and-or related to tax-customs-accounting background, your requests or messages may be kept on file for our records.
Marketing Communication
Our customer's privacy is top important . We do not release any customer’s details to other groups for the purpose of marketing or communications without your prior agreement. SANSHA operates an “I CONFIRM”
option for anyone choosing to receive marketing information from SANSHA. You may
“CHECK OUT”
of email communication or paper communication by clicking on the un-subscribe link in any of our marketing emails.
Disclosure of Information
We may disclose your personal data to the following third parties, for the following purposes:
Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006, where these companies assist us in providing services or otherwise administering our group operations;
Our partners and licensees who manage SANSHA for us in certain territories so that they may provide you with relevant SANSHA content and marketing in your local area;
Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score.
Our third party suppliers and professional advisors, who may need access to your personal data in order to provide services to us.
We may disclose your personal data to third parties in some cases:
Should we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If SANSHA assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property of SANSHA , our customers, or other parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations to avoid fraud and reduce risk.
The information disclosed above will be the minimum required for each party.
SANSHA does not sell, or give away, any personal information to any entity.
Where We Store Your Personal Data
The data we collect from you may be handled,processed, transferred to, or stored at, a destination outside of the European Economic Area , including countries where you may have fewer legal rights that you do under the laws of your own country. Personal data may also be processed by staff operating outside the European Economic Area who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing, or processing. We will take all steps necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.
Deleting Your Account
You can close your account with us at any time by contacting our customer service team at changedetails@sansha.com. If you choose to close your account, please note that you will need to re-open it at a later date, should you decide to make a new purchase.
We will delete the personal data associated with your account within a reasonable period, other than personal data which we have a need to retain for our internal business records (for example, data related to purchasing history).
Contact Us
SANSHA is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998. You have the right to access the information which SANSHA
holds about you and your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
You may contact us to modify your details at any time by emailing to: changedetails@sansha.com or in writing to any SANSHA office in your country
We may ask you to confirm your identity in order to amend data.
Cookie Policy
Cookies are codes which ask permission to be installed on a computer or any connected device. Once agreed, the file is added and it then allows SANSHA
to fine-tune our content to fit your needs and to improve your shopping experience. “Session Cookies” identify a session and are deleted after closing the session and “Permanent Cookies” permanently store browsing history on your data medium. We also use third party Cookies on our Website to improve our products and services.
A cookie does not gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept, restrict or decline cookies. Most web browsers will automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer.
Please note that cookies are computer specific, so if you log on to any website from a different computer, the cookie settings on that computer will apply.
By using the SANSHA website you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Certain features of our website cannot function without them.
Cookies in use, and their usage:
Cookie name
Cookie purpose
Session
This cookie allows our web servers to respond to your actions on the website such as "Add to basket" or browsing the website. The website wouldn't work for you without it.
Google Analytics_utma_utmb_utmc_utmz
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Information about the types of cookies used by Google can be found here - https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/
Google Adwords_utma_utmb_utmc_utmz
Google Adwords use the same cookies as Google Analytics.
__utma,
__utma,
__utma,
__utma,
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Information about the types of cookies used by Google can be found here - https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/
Affiliate Windowaw6427
This provides information to the Affiliate Window network to identify website users who have used an affiliate link to make a visit to the website. Information about the types of cookies used by Affiliate Window can be found here - http://blog.affiliatewindow.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/
Future
changes to this
privacy policy will be posted on this page.
Newsletter
Please sign up for our newsletter to know about our latest promotions, sales and exciting new fashion collections. At SANSHA, we are all fanatic dance lovers, and we are committed to bring fabulous dance goods to the dancing community.
We use cookies to make your experience better.
To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Learn more.
Allow Cookies
© 1982 - 2020 Sansha Group. All Rights Reserved.
